press75.com 2016-10-20

# Privacy Policy - Premium WordPress Themes by Press75

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Press75 we have a few key principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

_It is Press75’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites._

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Press75 collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Press75’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Press75’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Press75 may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Press75 also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blog. Press75 only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Press75’s websites choose to interact with Press75 in ways that require Press75 to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Press75 gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who purchase a product at [press75.com](http://press75.com/) to provide their name, a username, and an email address. Press75 collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitors interaction with Press75. Press75 does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Press75 may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Press75 may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Press75 does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Press75 discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Press75’s behalf or to provide services available at Press75’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Press75’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Press75 will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Press75 discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Press75 believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Press75, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of Press75 website and have supplied your email address, Press75 may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Press75 and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Press75 takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitors computer, and that the visitors browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Press75 uses cookies to help Press75 identify and track visitors, their usage of Press75 website, and their website access preferences. Press75 visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Press75’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Press75’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**

If Press75, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Press75 goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Press75 may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Press75 may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Press75’s sole discretion. Press75 encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

This Privacy Policy was written from [Automattic’s](http://automattic.com/privacy/), which is available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license.
